savepath.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy | SavePathDeals.com

**Introduction:**

We respect your privacy, and we are committed to protecting your privacy. We understand the importance of the information you entrust to us. In general, we respect your information and treat it as private and confidential. We will not typically give, sell, rent, exchange or otherwise provide your information with anyone else without prior consent or full disclosure. 

We will notify users of updates to this policy by noting the date of new changes directly below this statement. 

This policy was last amended June 9, 2012. Policy effective June 9, 2012. 

The following sections below describe our privacy practices concerning the information collected through our websites, our toolbars, and our applications in a clear and concise way. Below we generally describe what information we collect when you use our service, how we protect that information, how long we retain it, whom we share it with, and what your privacy options are. 

By using our website, toolbars, or applications, you consent to our collection and use of your data as described in this privacy policy. If you install the Savepath Deals application(s), you will be subject to Savepath Deals. End User License Agreement (EULA) that describes what information we collect when you use our applications and how that information may be used. 

**Information Collected:**

Some information that may be collected when you use Savepath Deals and/or the applications. We use cookies on our sites to collect and store this information: 

  * IP address of computer
  * Browser type (Internet Explorer 8, etc.)
  * Browser language setting
  * Other browser information (e.g. size, connection speed)
  * Date and time you access our site
  * Operating system or platform (Mac, Windows XP, etc.)
  * Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site (i.e. URL of the last webpage you visited before coming to our site)
  * Your activity on our site(s) and application(s) such as your queries, search results selected, clicks, pages viewed, etc.
  * If you install our application(s), when you start your browser, the application(s) sends a configuration request which also includes information about the specific release date and distribution source of your application(s).

When you install the Applications, we assign a unique identification code to your copy of the Applications, and such code is written to your computer's registry. This identification code is for application support purposes only. Further, the data collected does not provide personally identifiable information nor will this data be provided to any third parties. 

**Purpose of Information Collection:**

We use this information to measure the number of visitors to different sections of the site, to diagnose and correct system errors, and to improve the site. We do not connect this information to your name or identity, and we periodically delete this information from the server. 

In addition, the data collected can help us to understand our users (their demographics, what site features they like, how they use them, etc), to show you ads on our site and in our applications that are more relevant to you, to respond to your queries with the best possible search results, and to distinguish the install of the application in order to monitor the quality of our partner sites and distribution channels. 

We make limited use of cookies on this site for convenience features and to identify and prevent click fraud patterns. These cookies are only accessible within our servers and are typically deleted as soon as possible. 

**Data Collection Time Period:**

Your search queries are always anonymous in our system and not subject to data collection time period schedules. 

Cookies and configuration settings in connection with our application(s) are reset every 24 hours, but the information collected is stored in a query log for up to six months. 

**Data Collection and Sharing with Third Parties:**

Our sites contains links to other websites, including sites that we do not own or operate. Unless otherwise expressly stated, Savepath Deals. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites use of any information collected when Site visitors click through links to those sites. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policies of websites linked to our sites. 

Advertisers and advertising networks place ads (including sponsored links in search results) on our sites and in our applications. These companies may collect information, such as your computer's IP address, browser information, and search queries, as you use our services. They also may use web technologies such as cookies to collect data about you when you visit our sites. 

We will not share information we collected about you with any third party for other purposes (including direct marketing) without first obtaining your consent. 

We may disclose data we collect about our users when we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or respond to suspected illegal or fraudulent activity or to protect the safety, rights, or property of us, our users, or others. However, we do not collect any personally identifiable information. 

We may transfer your information to a third party if we or any of our affiliates are involved in a corporate restructuring (e.g., a sale, merger, or other transfer of assets). 

**Opt Out:**

If you want to disable the cookies placed on your computer by advertising companies that display ads on our site to prevent them from using information about you for targeting purposes, you can use the opt-out feature at http://www.networkadvertising.org/. 

**Security of Collected Information**

Although we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you, we have implemented security measures to prevent unauthorized or unlawful access to and misuse of the information we collect, including technological and physical security measures as well as procedural safeguards. However, because no security system can be 100% effective, we cannot completely guarantee the security of any information we may have collected from or about you. 

**Information From Children Under 13**

We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we determine that a user is under 13, we will immediately delete all information pertaining to that user. 

**Government Authorities and Legal Rights**

If requested or required by government authorities, such as law enforcement authorities, courts, or regulators, or otherwise to comply with the law, we may disclose any information we have about our users or modify other practices described in this policy, such as how long and in what form we keep information. We also may disclose information collected about you in order to exercise or protect legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

**Information Collected From Users Located Outside the USA**

If you are visiting our sites from outside the United States, your data will be transferred to and stored in our servers in the U.S. By using our sites, you consent to our collection and use of your data as described in this privacy policy.
